<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gumbo on Jeremiah Jones</title>
    <link>/gumbo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gumbo on Jeremiah Jones</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2022 Jeremiah Jones
</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 21:52:20 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/gumbo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello!</title>
      <link>/gumbo/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2022 21:52:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gumbo/hello/</guid>
      <description>It can be cold here in Rochester, but you still get a warm welcome!
   I hope you enjoy perusing this site! When I&amp;rsquo;m not writing proofs, creating software, or developing new methods, I&amp;rsquo;m playing with my dog, enjoying my wife&amp;rsquo;s singing, or tinkering with technology. I&amp;rsquo;ll be talking about a lot of this in this section.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schubert</title>
      <link>/gumbo/schubert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 19:14:17 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gumbo/schubert/</guid>
      <description>This is my dog, Schubert! My wife and I named him after one of our favorite composers.
Nicknames: &amp;ldquo;Schub&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Schuby-doo&amp;rdquo;
Favorite toy: Allie the Alligator
Favorite time: Toss-up between playtime and cuddle time
 I think he appreciates classical music.   --</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guitar</title>
      <link>/gumbo/guitar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 18:43:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gumbo/guitar/</guid>
      <description>I am a very spirited, if not incredibly talented, guitar player. I first picked up the proverbial axe in the 8th grade, and began a lifelong study of music with its help.
I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fascinated by the sonic effects achieved with the electric guitar. Arguably, entire sub-genres of music have evolved around certain achievable sounds with the electric guitar. From the crystalline sounds of Wes Montgomery, the gritty sounds of BB King, the cranked tones of 70&amp;rsquo;s-era Rush, to the hardly-recognizable sounds of modern metal; all these sounds are achieved by the processed sounds of magnets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source</title>
      <link>/gumbo/open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 18:43:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/gumbo/open-source/</guid>
      <description>What is open source software? It&amp;rsquo;s free! Not necessarily free as in &amp;ldquo;free lunch,&amp;rdquo; but &amp;ldquo;free as in freedom&amp;rdquo;&amp;mdash;freedom to use software without restriction, tweak the code at will, and liberty from annoying features just &amp;ldquo;because the developer said so.&amp;rdquo; Open source software allows creativity and innovation by allowing tinkerers, developers, and users to decide what they want from their software. I&amp;rsquo;ve been using open-source products and tools for years. My education and professional work has been empowered by R / Rstudio, Ubuntu, and Python.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
